MOOKHO MAKUTSOANE

CONTACT

3

061 3576 491

 \checkmark

boitumelomercy@gmail.co



Free State

EDUCATION

TETO HIGH SCHOOL

National Senior Certificate (Matric) 2009 - 2013

DIPLOMA IN DESIGN AND STUDIO ART

Central University of Technology

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

WeThinkCode_ 2023 - 2024

2014 - 2017

SKILLS

Design Thinking

Adobe Creative Suite

Adobe Photoshop CS5, CS6 and CC

Adobe Illustrator CS5, CS6 and CC

Adobe InDesign CS5, CS6 and CC

Front End Coding

Backend Tech

Problem-Solving

Computer Literacy

Strong Communication

SUMMARY

Experienced and professional graphic designer with five years in Branding, Brand Development, Social Media Marketing, Visual Communication, and Advertising. Possess strong creative and analytical skills, with an eye for detail. Enjoy collaborating with team members to achieve project goals. Currently completing final year of Software Development.

EXPERIENCE

ON BUSINESS: ART MUSEUM GUIDE

Oliewenhuis Art museum

2018 - 2019

- giving tours to schools and public.
- installation of new exhibition.
- administration.

ON BUSINESS: GRAPHIC DESIGNER

International Agricultural Academy for Africa (Designer)

2019 - 2020

- Managed graphic design from conception to delivery (Planning and managing all stages of the design projects).
- Ensured branding consistency through different marketing campaigns.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGN FOR IVY AFRICA

Ivy Africa

2020 - 2022

- Designed Brochure Designs for Social Media and print.
- Designed Monthly content design for social media publishing.
- Designed Services pricelist for Social Media slideshow and for print.
- Designed customer vouchers and services promotional designs.
- Rebranded business logo, business cards and letterhead design.